Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: November 2021

**Privacy Notice and Acceptance**

At Coventry Direct, protecting your privacy is one of our highest priorities. This Privacy Policy describes our privacy and security policies and practices. By using CoventryDirect.com (the “Website”), you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

**What Kind of Information Do We Collect?**

In the course of evaluating and qualifying life insurance policies we collect information from several sources, including insurance companies, agents, brokers, representatives, doctors, hospitals, and others. The information we receive includes, without limitation:

* Personal information, such as an insured’s name, address, Social Security number, tax identification number, other identification numbers issued by governmental bodies, email address, and telephone number;
* Health and medical information, such as doctor and hospital records, prescription information, and life expectancy evaluations;
* Life insurance and annuity information, such as the type of policy and the terms of the policy, a copy of the application, payment history, and a policy illustration;
* Transactional information, such as the terms of any life settlement contracts;
* Consumer reporting information; and
* Recordings of telephone calls with our representatives and call centers.

When you visit the Website, we may obtain information that you provide directly to us when you interact with the Website (e.g., when you use our chat feature, fill out our contact form, submit a life insurance policy for evaluation, or request more information from us). This information may include personal information about you, such as your name, email address, and phone number, and details about any life insurance policy you submit, including the insured’s medical history, age, and gender.

If you submit to us someone else’s personal information (e.g., their contact information or life insurance policy information), you represent that you have the authorization to provide this information to us.

**What Do We Do With the Information We Collect?**

The information we collect is used for: (i) evaluating and qualifying insureds and life insurance policies for life settlements and other products; (ii) communicating with you, including responding to your requests or inquiries; (iii) quality, training, and security purposes; (iv) detecting, preventing, investigating, identifying, reporting, or taking any other action with regard to any suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity or activity that violates our policies, including reporting insurance fraud; (v) carrying out market research and analysis; (vi) providing and developing marketing information; (vii) managing our internal operations; (viii) responding to complaints; (ix) complying with applicable laws, regulations, or legal processes as well as industry standards and our company policies; (x) establishing and defending our legal rights; and (xi) any other purpose, with your consent.

Information collected through the Website may be used for additional purposes, including: (i) facilitating and personalizing your user experience; (ii) monitoring and analyzing trends, usage, and activities of Website visitors and users; and (iii) improving the website.

**How Do We Share the Information We Collect?**

We may sell or disclose information about you to our affiliates and to nonaffiliated brokers, providers or other third parties in the course of evaluating and qualifying the respective life insurance policies.

Additionally, we may disclose personal information when required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal processes; in response to activities that are unlawful or a violation of our rules for use of the Website; or to protect and defend our rights or property.

**Who Has Access To Your Information In Our Records?**

We use a system of safeguards designed to protect against unauthorized access to your nonpublic personal information contained in our records. These protections include appropriate physical, electronic and procedural practices. We have policies in place restricting access to your information to only those individuals and entities who need to know the information for the above purposes. We educate our employees about the terms of this Privacy Policy and the essential nature of confidentiality and consumer privacy.

**How Does CoventryDirect.com Use Cookies, Advertising, and Online Tracking?  
**

Like most websites, CoventryDirect.com uses cookies and other tracking technologies to optimize your digital experience. Information collected by these tracking technologies may include IP addresses, device identifiers, browser characteristics, operating system details, internet service provider details, language preferences, referring URLs, time and length of visits, and pages viewed. These tracking technologies may be used by us or third parties to collect personal information about your online activities over time and across different devices and online properties when you use the Website.

“Cookies” are small data files stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies may allow a website to recognize a user’s device, record user preferences, track the pages a user clicks on while visiting the Website, and identify the website visited immediately beforehand. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies “turned on” so that we can offer you a better online experience. Blocking cookies may affect the availability and functionality of the Website and other websites or even invalidate opt outs that use cookies to recognize devices that have opted out.

Our vendors, including Facebook and Google, may use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information about your internet usage, including your use of this Website, and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. We and our vendors may use first-party cookies or other first-party identifiers as well as third-party cookies or other third-party identifiers to deliver advertisements, create a generalized user profile, measure user interests, approximate the geolocation of your device, and personalize content for you.

We may use certain web analytics services, including Google Analytics, to help us understand and analyze how visitors use the Website and to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. We’ve implemented Google Analytics Advertising features, including, but not limited to remarketing with analytics, interest-based advertising, demographics and interests reporting, user segment analysis, and impression reporting. For more information on how Google Analytics uses data collected through the Website, visit [policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites). You may also be able to opt out of Google Analytics by visiting [tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). For more information about third party cookies and other tracking technologies, including information about how to opt out of these technologies,visit [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). In addition, you may opt out of Google’s network of interest-based advertising at [adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/) and Facebook Custom Audiences by logging into your Facebook account and changing your privacy or advertising settings.

You may be able to opt out of certain interest-based advertising using the settings on your device. Your web browser may have settings that allow you to transmit a “Do Not Track” signal when you visit various websites or use online services. Like many websites, the Website is not designed to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from browsers. To learn more about “Do Not Track” signals, visit [www.allaboutdnt.com](https://allaboutdnt.com/).

**Third Party Privacy Practices.**

Coventry Direct is not responsible for the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties such as insurance companies, annuity providers, agents, brokers, or other service providers or entities. We are not responsible for the collection, usage and disclosure policies and practices (including the data security practices) of other organizations, such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Apple, Google, Microsoft, or any other software application developer or provider, social media platform, operating system or wireless service provider, or device manufacturer, including with respect to any information you disclose on Coventry Direct’s social media pages.

The Website may include links to other websites that are not owned or operated by Coventry Direct. This Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites, which may have their own privacy policies or notices that you should review to understand how they may collect, use, or disclose your personal information. Coventry Direct is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any linked websites that it does not control.

**Use of Coventry Direct Website by Minors.**

The Website is not directed to individuals under the age of eighteen (18) and we request that these individuals do not provide personal information through the Website. If we learn that individual under the age of eighteen (18) has provided us with personal information, we will delete it or otherwise comply with applicable law.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy.**

We reserve the right to modify or supplement our Privacy Policy at any time in accordance with applicable law or our business practices. We will indicate changes to the Privacy Policy by updating the “Last Updated” date at the beginning of the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after any update to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

**How to Contact Us.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact [info@coventrydirect.com](mailto:info@coventrydirect.com).
